Guide to the Records of Office of the Vice President for External Affairs and the Office of the Vice President for University Relations, John J. O'Connor RG.7.2
New York University Archives
Records of the Office of the Vice President for University Relations (John J. O'Connor)
1981-1995
New York University Archives
O'Connor, John J.
RG.7.2
32 Linear Feet in 51 boxes
This collection documents John J. O'Connor's tenure at NYU as Assistant to the Vice President for External Affairs and Associate Vice President for External Affairs. It also includes some records from his work as Vice President for University Relations. The colleciton is unprocessed.
Access Restrictions
Institutional records of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation (the date on which each document was written). Board of Trustees records are similarly closed for 35 years from the date of creation. The opening date for files spanning several years will be 20 years from the most recent date. Access will be given to material already 20 years old contained within a collection that is not yet open when such material can be isolated from the rest of the collection.
Materials related to personnel, faculty grievances, job searches and all files with information that falls under the University's Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) policy are permanently restricted.
Please contact the University Archivist with specific questions regarding restrictions.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged topically.
The files are grouped into 1 series:
Missing Title
Administrative Files
Historical/Biographical Note
John J. O'Connor first came to NYU in 1981 with incoming NYU President John Brademas, for whom he had worked as press secretary and special assistant on Capitol Hill. O'Connor assumed two positions at the university. He served as Executive Assistant to the President and worked under Naomi Levine, Vice President for External Affairs. The Office of External Affairs was responsible for the management and planning of all fundraising, public relations, and alumni programs. The duties of the office included the supervision of the Alumni Federation and the Office of University Development, which was concerned with fundraising activities designed to secure financial support form private sources. The Vice President also supervised the activities of the Office of Public Affairs, which operated the University Press Office, the Office of Advertising and Publications, which included the Photographic Department, and Reprographic Services.
In 1988, NYU reorganized several administrative offices "to meet the challenges of the next stage of advance of the University." As part of this reorganization, O'Connor became Vice President for University Relations. In this position he became responsible for all federal, state, and community relations, public affairs, special events and Commencement, alumni relations, and writing, research and editorial services. O'Connor continued as Executive Assistant to the President.
In 1996, O'Connor became acting vice chancellor at the State University of New York.
Sources:
Administration, Archives H, NYU Archives
Faculty Handbook, 1982, NYU Archives
Provenance
The collection was transferred to the University Archives in 1993 by John O'Connor.
Scope and Content Note
This collection documents O'Connor's tenure as Assistant to the Vice President for External Affairs and Associate Vice President for External Affairs. It also includes some records from his work as Vice President for University Relations. The colleciton is unprocessed.
Separated Material
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials that have been physically separated or removed.
Reports.; Private universities and colleges -- Administration -- United States.; Correspondence.; New York University. Office of External Affairs; New York University. Office of University Relations; O'Connor, John J.
- Series I. Administrative Files
  - JB Correspondence, Apr 1987-Jun 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - JB Correspondence 7/89-10/89, ca.Jul 1989-Oct 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence 12/88, Dec 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence 11/88, Nov 1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Oct 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, May 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Feb 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Mar 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Telephone Reports, Sep 1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Telephone Reports, Aug 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Telephone Reports, Sep 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Telephone Reports, Aug 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Telephone Reports, Aug 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Telephone Reports, Aug 1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sep 1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Telephone Reports, Aug 1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Telephone Reports, Sep 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Telephone Reports, Aug 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Telephone Reports, Jan 1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Telephone Reports Miscellaneous, Oct 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Telephone Charges, Jul 1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Phone Charges, Sep 1987-Nov 1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Phone Charges, Jan 1988-Feb 1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Phone Charges, Mar 1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Phone Charges, Apr 1988-May 1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Phone Charges, Jun 1988-Jul 1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence--Alumni Relations, Jan 1983-Dec 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence--Alumni Relations, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Buildings, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Brennan Documentary, May 1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Brademas Photos, Mar 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - NYU Photo Dept.--photos, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Council, 19851986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Credit Card, Jun 1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Alzheimer's Disease Center, May 1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - All University Dinner-Dance, Sep 1987-Oct 1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Advertising & Publications, May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Alumni, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Alumni, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - JB Speeches, Oct 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Governor Cuomo, Jan 1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Copyright, Apr 1983 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Continuing Education, Sep 1983 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Congressional Competitivess Caucus Recommendations, Jun 1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Assoc. Dues, Letters, Nov 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Alfonsin Convocation, Mar 1985-May 1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Alumni, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Alumni, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Alumni, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Alfonsin, President of Spain, Aug 1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Alumni Relations, Nov 1987-Jan 1988 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Fed-Varsity Club, misc. binder, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Photo Album--Brademas, U. of Pitt. Commencement, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bobst Library, Jun 1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bocconi Univ., Dec 1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - John Brademas, 1987-1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - John Brademas--book, Mar 1987-Aug 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Brademas biography, Aug 1983-Sep 1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Brademas Language, May 1987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Brademas Organizations, May 1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - JB memo to Alumni Fed., Dec 1987 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - American Council of Educ. Fellow, Jun 1987 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Annual Giving, Nov 1984-Jan 1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report, Nov 1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Art Department, Jun 1987 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Asbestos, Sep 1987 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Avery Fsher Center, Apr 1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Avery Fisher Dedication, May 1986 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Aquino, Sep 1986 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Bobst Dinner, Mar 1987 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Development Computers, 19861987 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Computers, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Commencement, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Commencement, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - COFEP, Sep 1987 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - CICU, Sep 1983 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Chatham House Foundation, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Cuomo Council pt. 1 of 2, 1983-1988 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Cuomo Council pt. 2 of 2, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Alumni Relations, May 1983-Nov 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Relations, Dec 1985-May 1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Community Relations, Feb 1983-Apr 1987 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - John O'Connor Correspondence, Jan 1986-May 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - John O'Connor Correspondence, Aug 1985-Jan 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - John O'Connor Correspondence, Aug 1985-Dec 1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Government Affairs, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Government Affairs, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Government Affairs, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Leo Jaffe Theatre Dedication, Mar 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Karamanalis Visit, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Kriser Dental Center Dedication, Nov 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Lybimov Luncheon, Mar 1986 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Oxford Trip, Apr 1989 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Special Events, Oct 1985 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Public Affairs, Jul 1978-Dec 1987 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Recent Alumni Events, Nov 1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Special Events, Sep 1983-Dec 1983 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Ward, Benjamin, Mar 1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Zuccaro, Ron, Apr 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Feb 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Mar 1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, May 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1986 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Oct 1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Nov 1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Dec 1986 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Telephone, Alumni Federation, Aug 1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Telephone, Aug 1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Telephone, Aug 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Telephone, Phonathon, Aug 1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Telephone, Aug 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Telephone,NYU Magazine, Aug 1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Telephone, Aug 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Telephone,Special Events, Aug 1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Telephone, Aug 1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Telephone, Aug 1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Telephone,Alumni Fundraising Project, 6.401. 654. 214, Aug 1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Telephone, Sep 1989 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Telephone,Public Affairs, Sep 1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Telephone, Sep 1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Telephone, University Relations, Sep 1989 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Telephone, Sep 1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Telephone, Community and Government Relations 2.040.176, Sep 1989 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Telephone, Sep 1989 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Telephone, Alumni Relations, Sep 1989 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Telephone, Sep 1989 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Telephone,Phonathon, Sep 1989 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Telephone, Sep 1989 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Telephone, NYU Magazine, Sep 1989 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Telephone, Sep 1989 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Telephone, Special Events, Sep 1989 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Telephone, Sep 1989 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Telephone, Oct 1989 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Telephone, Public Affairs, Oct 1989 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Telephone, Oct 1989 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Telephone, University Relations, Oct 1989 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Telephone, Oct 1989 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Telephone, Community and Government Relations, Oct 1989 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Telephone, Oct 1989 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Telephone, Alumni Relations, Oct 1989 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Telephone, Oct 1989 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Telephone, Phonathon, Oct 1989 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Telephone, NYU Magazine, Oct 1989 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Telephone, Oct 1989 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Telephone, Special Events, Oct 1989 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Telephone, Oct 1989 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Telephone, Alumni Federation, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Telephone, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Telephone, Public Affairs, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Telephone, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Telephone, University Relations, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Telephone, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Telephone, Community and Government Reations, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Telephone, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Telephone, Alumni Relations, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Telephone, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Telephone, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Telephone, Phonathon, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Telephone, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Telephone, NYU Magazine, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Telephone, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Telephone, Special Events, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Telephone, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Telephone, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Telephone, Alumni Fundraising Project, Nov 1989 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Telephone, Alumni Federation, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Telephone, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Telephone, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Telephone, Public Affairs, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Untitled, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Telephone, University Relations, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Telephone, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Telephone, Community and Government Relations, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Telephone, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Telephone, Alumni Relations, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Telephone, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Telephone, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Telephone, Phonathon, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Telephone, Alumni Fundraising, Info Systems, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Telephone, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Telephone, NYU Magazine, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Telephone, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Telephone, Special Events, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Telephone, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Telephone, Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Benton Foundation, Jul 1984 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Billington, James, Aug 1987 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Employment, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Government Affairs, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - JB Correspondence, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Annual Report, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Arp Sculpture dedication, Sep 1987 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Bobst Dinner, Oct 1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Bobst Dinner, Oct 1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Commencement, Photographs, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Commencement, Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Commencement, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Commencement, Rain Plan, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Commencement, Miscellaneous, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Commencement, Staffing, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Dukakis Campaign, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Employment, Jul 1983-Sep 1987 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Father Hesburgh Dinner, Oct 1983 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Florence Trip, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Florence Trip (La Pietra), 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees Forence Trip, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Government Relations, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Government Affairs, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Government Affairs, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Image Task Force, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Inauguration, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Muskie Dinner and Lecture, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Photographs, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Feb 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Mar 1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1987 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, May 1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Oct 1987 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Nov 1987 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Dec 1987 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Feb 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Mar 1989 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, May 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1989 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Oct 1989 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Nov 1989 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Dec 1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Feb 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Mar 1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, May 1990 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Oct 1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Nov 1990 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Dec 1990 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1991 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Feb 1991 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Mar 1991 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1991 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, May 1991 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1991 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1991 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1991 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1991 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Oct 1991 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Nov 1991 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Dec 1991 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - AAU, Nov 1988-Nov 1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Admissions, Jun 1989-Oct 1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Alumni, Apr 1985-Dec 1988 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Alumni, Jan 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Council, Nov 1987-Dec 1988 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Council, Sep 1988-Dec 1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees, Oct 1989 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - BSR, Jan 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Bulgarian American Exchange of Researchers, May 1989 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Columbian Journalists, Sep 1989-Oct 1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Commencement, Mar 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Community Relations, Oct 1988-Dec 1989 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Relations, Apr 1988-Dec 1989 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Courant Institute, Oct 1984-Aug 1989 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Dental Centre, Jan 1985-Nov 1989 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Development, Apr 1983-Sep 1985 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Development, Sep 1986-Jan 1987 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - East-West Business Dynamics Center, Oct 1989-Apr 1990 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Ellis Island Preservation Project, Jan 1983-Jun 1989 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Employment, Aug 1987-Oct 1989 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Employee Education Assistance, Feb 1988 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Campaign, Jan 1985 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Housing, Jan 1985 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Salary, Mar 1989-Nov 1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Founders Day, Mar 1987-Nov 1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Ministers Conference, May 1987 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - French Revolution Bicentennial Celebration, Mar 1987-May 1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Gannett Center Fellows, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Georgetown, Sep 1989 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Government Affairs, Jan 1989-Sep 1989 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Government Affairs, Sep 1989-Oct 1989 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Government Affairs, Oct 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Object Codes, Sep 1988-Aug 1989 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Book, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Book, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Book, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Appointment Book, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Appointment Book, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Government Relations, Nov 1988-Dec 1989 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - GPA Cost Allocation, Apr 1986-Oct 1988 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Grant Proposals, Jun 1987-Aug 1987 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Handicap, Apr 1984-Apr 1989 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Hanifin, Tovah [Michael], Aug 1987 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Hayden Hall, Feb 1986 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Heights Alumni Lounge, Mar 1987-May 1988 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Hill and Knowlton, Oct 1987 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Human Resources Center, Jul 1985-Jan 1986 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Hebrew Union, Aug 1986-Sep 1986 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - IBM, Aug 1989 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Japanese Center, Jan 1982-Mar 1985 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Japanese Project, Mar 1983 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Kaufman, Bruce [Dir. Alumni Relations], Apr 1986-Jan 1988 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Kevorkian Center, Dec 1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kriser Winner, Apr 1985 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - La Pietra, Mar 1986-Jun 1986 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Latin American Studies, Mar 1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Testimony, Nov 1969-Nov 1972 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Library Convocation, Nov 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Naomi Levine, Jul 1983-Aug 1983 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Loeb, Mar 1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Jill Long, Jun 1986 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - London Bus, Mar 1988 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Mailick Project, Mar 1983-May 1983 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Manville Trust Fund, Oct 1989 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Maragall, Pascual (Mayor of Barcelona), Jun 1989 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Marnold Fellow, Nov 1987 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Mayoral Debates Program, Jul 1989Aug 1989 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Macintosh, Aug 1984 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Medicare (Catastrophic Illness), Feb 1987 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Medical Center, Biomedical Research Building, Sep 1987-Oct 1987 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Medical Research Training, Mar 1987 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Mitterand Visit, Jan 1989-Feb 1989 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Matt Miller, Apr 1987 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Mondale for President, Jun 1983-Sep 1983 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - National Public Service Program, Feb 1986 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - National Arts Education Research Center, Sep 1987 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Anthropology Journal, Jun 1983 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - New York Stock Exchange, Jun 1983 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - NYU "bio", Apr 1989 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - NYU club, Mar 1989 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - NYU Magazine (1 of 2), Nov 1985-Feb 1991 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - NYU Magazine (2 of 2), Nov 1985-Feb 1991 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - NYU Magazine, Distribution, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - New York University Press, Jan 1985-Sep 1991 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - NYU Report, Jun 1987-Aug 1987 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Operating Budget, Jun 1988 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - New Boston Group, Nov 1988 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Estate of Arthur M. Apman, Nov 1987 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - RW Johnson Foundation, Jun 1989 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Palm Beach, Jan 1984 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Pell Grant, Apr 1986 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Handicap Education, Jul 1985 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Polish People's Republic, Sep 1987 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Political Leaders, Jun 1983-Aug 1983 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Plaque, Nov 1986 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Salomon Lecture, Sep 1982 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Schaetzel, Robert (former ambassador), Apr 1986 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Sherman Project, Oct 1986 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Singapore University, May 1989 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Silverman, Henry, Aug 1987 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Simon & Schuster Student Travel Guide, Feb 1986-Mar 1986 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - 6 Year Report, May 1988 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Speech Writing, Jan 1984 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Super Conducting Supercollider, Jun 1987 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Tax Issues, Sep 1987 (Box 17, Folder 53)